[
  {
    "number": 1,
    "question": "Which of the following income is not taxable under the head income from salary?",
    "options": ["Salary of a Govt. employee", "Pension", "Salary of a Govt. employee posted abroad", "Salary of a member of parliament"],
    "answer": "Salary of a member of parliament"
  },
  {
    "number": 2,
    "question": "Any income from slump sale is taxable under:",
    "options": ["Income from other sources", "Capital gain", "Profits and gains from business or profession", "Income from house property"],
    "answer": "Capital gain"
  },
  {
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a casual income?",
    "options": ["Winning from lottery", "A gift from relative", "Habitual betting", "Income from card games"],
    "answer": "A gift from relative"
  },
  {
    "number": 4,
    "question": "Variable working capital is required to meet:",
    "options": ["Seasonal demand", "Special exigencies", "Temporary needs", "All of the above"],
    "answer": "All of the above"
  },
  {
    "number": 5,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a method of slowing cash outflows?",
    "options": ["Lock box system", "Centralization of payments", "Making use of float", "Reducing frequency of payments"],
    "answer": "Lock box system"
  },
  {
    "number": 6,
    "question": "Cost of capital is not similar to one of the following:",
    "options": ["Cut off rate", "Target rate", "Hurdle rate", "Internal Rate of Return"],
    "answer": "Target rate"
  },
  {
    "number": 7,
    "question": "Which of the following factor does not influence the capital structure decision?",
    "options": ["Cost of capital", "Risk", "Corporate tax", "Composition of fixed assets"],
    "answer": "Composition of fixed assets"
  },
  {
    "number": 8,
    "question": "Capital Index Bonds are linked with:",
    "options": ["BSE sensex", "NSE nifty", "Consumer price index", "BSE-100"],
    "answer": "Consumer price index"
  },
  {
    "number": 9,
    "question": "Open ended mutual fund schemes are:",
    "options": ["Open for a particular period", "Have fixed period of maturity", "Listed in the stock exchange", "Open on a continuous basis"],
    "answer": "Open on a continuous basis"
  },
  {
    "number": 10,
    "question": "Compulsory delisting of a company from stock market is due to:",
    "options": ["Violation of listing agreement", "Capital size is small", "Merger", "Thin trading"],
    "answer": "Violation of listing agreement"
  },
  {
    "number": 11,
    "question": "Market value of bond depends on:",
    "options": ["The coupon rate", "Years to maturity", "Expected yield to maturity", "All the above"],
    "answer": "All the above"
  },
  {
    "number": 12,
    "question": "What is the dividend yield of a stock having a face value of Rs. 10? Which has declared 35% dividend for the current year? The present market value of the stock is Rs. 40:",
    "options": ["35%", "70%", "8.75%", "8.5%"],
    "answer": "8.75%"
  },
  {
    "number": 13,
    "question": "Diversification of investments helps to reduce:",
    "options": ["Interest rate risk", "Market risk", "Unique risk", "Inflation risk"],
    "answer": "Unique risk"
  },
  {
    "number": 14,
    "question": "The put option buyer gains:",
    "options": ["In the bullish market", "In the bearish market", "In the stable market", "When the strike price is lower than stock price"],
    "answer": "In the bearish market"
  },
  {
    "number": 15,
    "question": "The mutual funds listed in the stock exchange are:",
    "options": ["Closed-end funds", "Open-end funds", "Growth schemes", "Stock index funds"],
    "answer": "Closed-end funds"
  },
  {
    "number": 16,
    "question": "Among the following which one represents a potential use of working capital:",
    "options": ["Sale of fixed assets at a loss", "Net loss from operation", "Declaration of dividend", "Payment to creditors"],
    "answer": "Payment to creditors"
  },
  {
    "number": 17,
    "question": "The father of scientific management is:",
    "options": ["F.W. Taylor", "F.E.L. Brach", "Peter. F. Drucker", "Michael. J. Jucious"],
    "answer": "F.W. Taylor"
  },
  {
    "number": 18,
    "question": "Periodical cost is also known as:",
    "options": ["Variable cost", "Revenue cost", "Marginal cost", "Fixed cost"],
    "answer": "Fixed cost"
  },
  {
    "number": 19,
    "question": "The process of delegation is always:",
    "options": ["Circular", "Horizontal", "Top down", "Bottom up"],
    "answer": "Top down"
  },
  {
    "number": 20,
    "question": "Management By Objective was developed as a philosophy by:",
    "options": ["Peter. F. Drucker", "F.W. Taylor", "Mayo", "Simon"],
    "answer": "Peter. F. Drucker"
  },
  {
    "number": 21,
    "question": "Financial structure represents:",
    "options": ["Long term liabilities", "Capital structure", "Long term and short term liabilities", "Working capital"],
    "answer": "Long term and short term liabilities"
  },
  {
    "number": 22,
    "question": "Usually dividend declared and paid as a percentage of:",
    "options": ["Authorized capital", "Issued capital", "Called up capital", "Paid up capital"],
    "answer": "Paid up capital"
  },
  {
    "number": 23,
    "question": "To determine the intrinsic value of share, which of the following data is essential:",
    "options": ["Dividend per share", "Market value per share", "Expected rate of return", "Net equity"],
    "answer": "Expected rate of return"
  },
  {
    "number": 24,
    "question": "In a fund flow statement (working capital basis) a current liability repaid by the organization:",
    "options": ["Is shown as a source of working capital", "Is shown as an application of working capital", "Is shown as a decrease in cash", "Do not affect the working capital"],
    "answer": "Is shown as an application of working capital"
  },
  {
    "number": 25,
    "question": "A manager who works with the help of rules and regulations is called:",
    "options": ["Traipest leader", "Laissez faire leader", "Participator leader", "Bureaucratic leader"],
    "answer": "Bureaucratic leader"
  },
  {
    "number": 26,
    "question": "Income Tax is imposed by:",
    "options": ["Central Govt.", "State Govt.", "Local authority", "Central and State Govt."],
    "answer": "Central Govt."
  },
  {
    "number": 27,
    "question": "Inflation can be checked through:",
    "options": ["Reducing public expenditure", "Increasing direct taxation", "Surplus budgeting", "All of these"],
    "answer": "All of these"
  },
  {
    "number": 28,
    "question": "Which of the following statement is/are true?<br>(1) Patent account is a nominal<br>(2) Capital account is a real account<br>(3) Prepaid rent is a personal account<br>(4) Outstanding salaries is a nominal account<br>(5) Drawings account is a nominal account",
    "options": [
      "Only (1) above",
      "Only (3) above",
      "Both (1) and (2) above",
      "(2), (3) and (5) above"
    ],
    "answer": "(2), (3) and (5) above"
  },
  {
    "number": 29,
    "question": "The major source of revenue to the Government is:",
    "options": ["Income tax other than corporate tax", "Corporate tax", "Wealth tax", "Gift tax"],
    "answer": "Corporate tax"
  },
  {
    "number": 30,
    "question": "Cost of acquisition of natural resources are allocated through:",
    "options": ["Depletion", "Depreciation", "Allocation", "Amortization"],
    "answer": "Depletion"
  },
  {
    "number": 31,
    "question": "The technique used to study the position and performance of an undertaking with focus on financial statement is termed as:",
    "options": ["Fundamental analysis", "Break even analysis", "Cross sectional analysis", "Technical analysis"],
    "answer": "Fundamental analysis"
  },
  {
    "number": 32,
    "question": "The marginal cost equation is:",
    "options": ["S-V=F+P", "S+V=F+P", "S=V-C", "S+C=FÂ±P"],
    "answer": "S-V=F+P"
  },
  {
    "number": 33,
    "question": "Capital of a company is raised in the following sequence:",
    "options": [
      "Issued, subscribed, called up, nominal",
      "Nominal, issued, called up, subscribed",
      "Issued, nominal, subscribed, called up",
      "Nominal, subscribed issued, called up"
    ],
    "answer": "Nominal, subscribed issued, called up"
  },
  {
    "number": 34,
    "question": "Contingent liabilities appearing as a note to balance sheet as a part of:",
    "options": ["Concept of full disclosure", "Consistency concept", "Conservatism concept", "Realization concept"],
    "answer": "Concept of full disclosure"
  },
  {
    "number": 35,
    "question": "The immediate solvency ratio is:",
    "options": ["Current ratio", "Quick ratio", "Debt equity ratio", "Stock turnover ratio"],
    "answer": "Quick ratio"
  },
  {
    "number": 36,
    "question": "Which of the following will result in decreasing margin of safety?",
    "options": ["Increase in variable cost", "Reduction in fixed cost", "Increase in selling price", "Change in sales mix in order to increase contribution"],
    "answer": "Increase in variable cost"
  },
  {
    "number": 37,
    "question": "In Maslow's Need Hierarchy Theory, in which of the following order human needs arise:",
    "options": [
      "Physiological needs, social needs, safety needs, ego needs, self actualization needs",
      "Physiological needs, social needs, ego needs, safety needs, self actualization needs",
      "Physiological needs, safety needs, social needs, ego needs, self actualization needs.",
      "Physiological needs, safety needs, ego needs, social needs, self actualization needs"
    ],
    "answer": "Physiological needs, safety needs, social needs, ego needs, self actualization needs."
  },
  {
    "number": 38,
    "question": "The activity which is not helpful in controlling money supply?",
    "options": ["CRR", "Free market policy", "Bank rate", "Change in margin requirements"],
    "answer": "Free market policy"
  },
  {
    "number": 39,
    "question": "'Stagflation' means:",
    "options": ["Inflation with depression", "Inflation with growth", "Deflation with growth", "Inflation after deflation"],
    "answer": "Inflation with depression"
  },
  {
    "number": 40,
    "question": "Purchase and distribution of imported products by Govt. is called:",
    "options": ["Cartel", "Canalization", "Grey marketing", "None of the above"],
    "answer": "Canalization"
  },
  {
    "number": 41,
    "question": "Generally, orientation is given to:",
    "options": ["Supervisory staff", "Clerical staff", "New entrants", "Previous employees"],
    "answer": "New entrants"
  },
  {
    "number": 42,
    "question": "Full cost pricing method means:",
    "options": ["Fixed cost plus mark-up", "All cost plus normal profit margin", "Standard cost plus mark-up", "Market price plus mark-up"],
    "answer": "All cost plus normal profit margin"
  },
  {
    "number": 43,
    "question": "When a balance sheet is arranged in liquidity order, which of the following is correct?",
    "options": [
      "Fixed assets, short term investments, cash and current assets",
      "Cash, short term investments, current assets, fixed assets",
      "Cash, current assets, short term investments, fixed assets",
      "Short term investments, cash, current assets, fixed assets"
    ],
    "answer": "Cash, short term investments, current assets, fixed assets"
  },
  {
    "number": 44,
    "question": "Risk involved in a firm is higher where:",
    "options": ["Cost of capital is low", "Cost of capital is high", "Cost of capital is neutral", "None of these"],
    "answer": "Cost of capital is high"
  },
  {
    "number": 45,
    "question": "In respect of planning, which of the following statement is incorrect?",
    "options": [
      "Planning is forward looking",
      "Planning is intellectual activity",
      "Planning is not performed by top management",
      "Planning is related to objectives"
    ],
    "answer": "Planning is not performed by top management"
  },
  {
    "number": 46,
    "question": "A company acquired assets worth Rs.1,98,000 and the purchase price is paid by issue of equity shares of Rs. 10 each at 10% discount. The number of shares issued:",
    "options": ["19,800", "20,000", "22,000", "18,000"],
    "answer": "22,000"
  },
  {
    "number": 47,
    "question": "Which one of the following is not a distinctive feature of co-operative organization?",
    "options": ["Service motto", "Democratic management", "One share one vote system", "Corporate status"],
    "answer": "Corporate status"
  },
  {
    "number": 48,
    "question": "Harish LTD furnished the following information:<br>10% preference share capital RS.12,00,000<br>12% debentures Rs.8,00,000<br>Equity share holders fund Rs.50,00,000<br>The capital gearing ratio of Harish LTD was:",
    "options": ["0.40", "0.60", "2.50", "0.16"],
    "answer": "0.40"
  },
  {
    "number": 49,
    "question": "Gopal LTD furnished the following information:<br>Return on total assets-10%<br>Return on net worth-20%<br>Net worth-10,00,000<br>The total assets of the company were:",
    "options": ["Rs. 10,00,000", "Rs. 20,00,000", "Rs. 12,00,000", "Rs. 15,00,000"],
    "answer": "Rs. 20,00,000"
  },
  {
    "number": 50,
    "question": "Y LTD has furnished the following information:<br>Period-I Sales-7,00,000 Profit/Loss-10,000(loss)<br>Period-II Sales-9,00,000 Profit/Loss-10,000<br>The variable cost of period II is:",
    "options": ["6,30,000", "7,20,000", "8,90,000", "8,10,000"],
    "answer": "7,20,000"
  },
  {
    "number": 51,
    "question": "Geethu LTD has furnished the following information:<br>Fixed cost Rs.1,50,000<br>Variable cost per unit Rs.10<br>Selling price per unit Rs.15<br>To brought down the break even point to 25000 unit, the selling price should be:",
    "options": ["Rs. 10", "Rs. 6", "Rs. 16", "Rs. 20"],
    "answer": "Rs. 16"
  },
  {
    "number": 52,
    "question": "Five 'm's of management are:",
    "options": [
      "Marketing, monitoring, motivation, machinery and methods",
      "Manager, muscle, machinery and methods",
      "Man, money, material, machinery and methods",
      "Marketing, man power, muscle, motivation and methods"
    ],
    "answer": "Man, money, material, machinery and methods"
  },
  {
    "number": 53,
    "question": "Current ratio = 2.8<br>Acid-test ratio = 1.5<br>Working capital = 1,62,000<br>The amount of current asset:",
    "options": ["90,000", "2,52,000", "1,35,000", "1,52,000"],
    "answer": "2,52,000"
  },
  {
    "number": 54,
    "question": "In life insurance, age of applicant and the insurance premium is:",
    "options": ["Positively correlated", "Negatively correlated", "Zero correlated", "None of the above"],
    "answer": "Positively correlated"
  },
  {
    "number": 55,
    "question": "Credit sales Rs.1,20,000<br>Debtors Rs.20,000<br>Bills receivable Rs.10,000<br>Average collection period is:",
    "options": ["4 months", "5 months", "3 months", "6 months"],
    "answer": "2 months"
  },
  {
    "number": 56,
    "question": "In determining the fund from operation gain on sale of fixed assets should be ___ from the net profit and the loss on sale of fixed asset should be ___ to the net profit.",
    "options": [
      "Added, deducted",
      "Added, added",
      "Deducted, added",
      "Deducted, deducted"
    ],
    "answer": "Deducted, added"
  },
  {
    "number": 57,
    "question": "Net profit-60,000<br>Total purchase-1,40,000<br>Opening creditors-48,000<br>Closing creditors-72,000<br>The amount of cash from operation will be:",
    "options": ["2,00,000", "60,000", "1,32,000", "84,000"],
    "answer": "84,000"
  },
  {
    "number": 58,
    "question": "Which of the following statement is the basis of diversification?",
    "options": [
      "It never rains, but it pours",
      "Make hay while the sun shines",
      "Don't look a gift horse in the mouth",
      "Don't put all your eggs in one basket"
    ],
    "answer": "Don't put all your eggs in one basket"
  },
  {
    "number": 59,
    "question": "Income received in India in the previous year is taxable in the hands of:",
    "options": ["Resident", "Not ordinarily resident", "Non resident", "All above"],
    "answer": "All above"
  },
  {
    "number": 60,
    "question": "Technical analysis helps:",
    "options": [
      "To find out the present state of stock market",
      "To estimate the growth of the stock market",
      "To show the direction of the stock market",
      "To indicate the economic activity"
    ],
    "answer": "To show the direction of the stock market"
  },
  {
    "number": 61,
    "question": "What is subscript?",
    "options": [
      "Text that is smaller and below the baseline",
      "Text that is smaller and above the baseline",
      "Text that is larger and below the baseline",
      "Text that is larger and above the baseline"
    ],
    "answer": "Text that is smaller and below the baseline"
  },
  {
    "number": 62,
    "question": "What language does the computer use and understand?",
    "options": ["High-level", "Assembly", "Machine", "None of the above"],
    "answer": "Machine"
  },
  {
    "number": 63,
    "question": "What is a firewall?",
    "options": ["Antivirus program", "Internet blocker", "Internet logger", "Internet filter"],
    "answer": "Internet filter"
  },
  {
    "number": 64,
    "question": "What is BIOS short for?",
    "options": [
      "Not short for anything",
      "Basic Input / Output System",
      "Binary Input / Output System",
      "Bus Input / Output System"
    ],
    "answer": "Basic Input / Output System"
  },
  {
    "number": 65,
    "question": "Which below IP address would be used for a local network?",
    "options": [
      "192.168.1.100",
      "69.72.169.241",
      "74.125.127.100",
      "209.131.36.100"
    ],
    "answer": "192.168.1.100"
  },
  {
    "number": 66,
    "question": "What does the term MIME stand for?",
    "options": [
      "Mail Internet Mail Exchange",
      "Mail Interleave Method Exchange",
      "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions",
      "Multipurpose Interleave Mail Exchange"
    ],
    "answer": "Multipurpose Internet Mail Extensions"
  },
  {
    "number": 67,
    "question": "Why should you avoid downloading files using file-sharing programs like Limewire or Frostwire?",
    "options": [
      "(A) Against Copy right laws",
      "(B) Risk of Viruses",
      "(C) High Penalty once Caught",
      "(A) (B) and (C)"
    ],
    "answer": "(A) (B) and (C)"
  },
  {
    "number": 68,
    "question": "What does the term IRQ stand for?",
    "options": [
      "Input Request Queue",
      "Interrupt Request Queue",
      "Interrupt Request",
      "Input Request"
    ],
    "answer": "Interrupt Request"
  },
  {
    "number": 69,
    "question": "Which Storage Technology is more durable?",
    "options": ["Magnetic Tape", "M-Disc", "Hard Disk", "DVD"],
    "answer": "M-Disc"
  },
  {
    "number": 70,
    "question": "The results of arithmetical and logical operations are stored in a / an:",
    "options": ["Accumulator", "Instruction register", "Cache", "ROM"],
    "answer": "Accumulator"
  },
  {
    "number": 71,
    "question": "Which of the following operating systems is produced by IBM?",
    "options": ["OS-2", "Windows", "DOS", "UNIX"],
    "answer": "OS-2"
  },
  {
    "number": 72,
    "question": "_____ is an error in computer programme.",
    "options": ["Virus", "Bug", "Crash", "Power Failure"],
    "answer": "Bug"
  },
  {
    "number": 73,
    "question": "Minimize all of the opened windows:",
    "options": [
      "Windows Logo + M",
      "Windows Logo",
      "Windows Logo + BREAK",
      "Windows Logo + D"
    ],
    "answer": "Windows Logo + M"
  },
  {
    "number": 74,
    "question": "_____ Provides a common address space and routes the packets of data across the entire Internet.",
    "options": ["UDP", "TCP", "FTP", "IP"],
    "answer": "IP"
  },
  {
    "number": 75,
    "question": "Who is considered to be The Father of Artificial Intelligence?",
    "options": ["George Boole", "John McCarthy", "Allen Newell", "Alan Turing"],
    "answer": "John McCarthy"
  },
  {
    "number": 76,
    "question": "The use of parity bit is for:",
    "options": ["Coding", "Indexing", "Error detection", "None of these"],
    "answer": "Error detection"
  },
  {
    "number": 77,
    "question": "One MB =",
    "options": ["1000 KB", "1024 Bytes", "10000 Bits", "210 KB"],
    "answer": "1024 Bytes"
  },
  {
    "number": 78,
    "question": "Programs stored in ROM Chips are called:",
    "options": ["Hardware", "Software", "Firmware", "None of these"],
    "answer": "Firmware"
  },
  {
    "number": 79,
    "question": "Which among is the fastest Super Computer?",
    "options": ["Stampede", "Tianhe-2", "Mira", "Param"],
    "answer": "Tianhe-2"
  },
  {
    "number": 80,
    "question": "Which Memory is more fast?",
    "options": ["ROM", "Secondary Memory", "RAM", "Cache Memory"],
    "answer": "Cache Memory"
  },
  {
    "number": 81,
    "question": "Which of the following Indian was honoured by a special Oscar Award?",
    "options": ["Mira Nair", "O.P. Sippy", "Satyajith Ray", "Mahesh Bhatt"],
    "answer": "Satyajith Ray"
  },
  {
    "number": 82,
    "question": "\"Equal Pay for Equal Work both Men and Women\" has been ensured in the Indian Constitution as:",
    "options": [
      "Directive Principles of State Policy",
      "Fundamental Right",
      "Fundamental Duties",
      "Economic Right"
    ],
    "answer": "Directive Principles of State Policy"
  },
  {
    "number": 83,
    "question": "The largest number of Buddhist's found in:",
    "options": ["Orissa", "Uttar Pradesh", "Madhya Pradesh", "Maharashtra"],
    "answer": "Maharashtra"
  },
  {
    "number": 84,
    "question": "The statement about a federal union composed of British Provinces is related to:",
    "options": ["Gandhi - Irwin Pact", "Cripps Mission", "Cabinet Mission", "Simon Commission"],
    "answer": "Cabinet Mission"
  },
  {
    "number": 85,
    "question": "Which among the following ports was called Babl-al-Makka (Gate of Makka) during the Mugal period?",
    "options": ["Calicut", "Surat", "Thoothukudi", "Vishakapattanam"],
    "answer": "Surat"
  },
  {
    "number": 86,
    "question": "Which Article of the Indian Constitution speaks that \"India, that is Bharat, shall be a Union of States\"?",
    "options": ["Article 1", "Article 2", "Article 4", "Article 5"],
    "answer": "Article 1"
  },
  {
    "number": 87,
    "question": "Monopolies and Restrictive Trade practices (Prevention) Act came into force on:",
    "options": ["January 1, 1970", "June 1, 1970", "December 2, 1970", "January 1, 1971"],
    "answer": "June 1, 1970"
  },
  {
    "number": 88,
    "question": "NABARD was setup on July 1, 1982 by taking over the functions of the agricultural credit department of RBI and:",
    "options": [
      "Agricultural Money Lending Corporation",
      "Agricultural Refinance and Development Corporations (ARDC)",
      "Central Agricultural Financing Corporation",
      "National Crop Insurance Organisation"
    ],
    "answer": "Agricultural Refinance and Development Corporations (ARDC)"
  },
  {
    "number": 89,
    "question": "Common Wealth Day is celebrated around the World on:",
    "options": [
      "2nd Monday in January",
      "2nd Monday in March",
      "2nd Monday in April",
      "2nd Monday in June"
    ],
    "answer": "2nd Monday in March"
  },
  {
    "number": 90,
    "question": "Japan shutdown its last nuclear power station on:",
    "options": [
      "September 12, 2013",
      "September 15, 2013",
      "September 22, 2013",
      "October 14, 2013"
    ],
    "answer": "September 15, 2013"
  },
  {
    "number": 91,
    "question": "National Communal Harmony Awards 2011-2012 was shared by:",
    "options": [
      "Khamliana of Mizoram and Mohammad Abdul Bari by Odisha",
      "Gopal Shukla of Jaipur and Mohammad Sulphikar of Jammu",
      "T.C. Shetty of Tamil Nadu and Gopalaswami of Bihar",
      "J.K. Singh of Punjab and Gopal Iyyankar of Kerala"
    ],
    "answer": "Khamliana of Mizoram and Mohammad Abdul Bari by Odisha"
  },
  {
    "number": 92,
    "question": "Which of the following countries opened the world's largest offshore wind farm on July 4, 2013?",
    "options": ["Canada", "China", "Switzerland", "Britain"],
    "answer": "Britain"
  },
  {
    "number": 93,
    "question": "World day against Child Labour is observed on:",
    "options": ["June 12", "June 22", "June 26", "June 28"],
    "answer": "June 12"
  },
  {
    "number": 94,
    "question": "The theme of World Habitat Day 2013 is:",
    "options": [
      "Changing cities, building opportunities",
      "Urban mobility to encourage people to shift towards more sustainable modes of transportation",
      "Pollution free cities and safe living",
      "Living together is happiness, protecting the rights of each other"
    ],
    "answer": "Urban mobility to encourage people to shift towards more sustainable modes of transportation"
  },
  {
    "number": 95,
    "question": "Sachin Tendulkar's last test match was with which country?",
    "options": ["South Africa", "Srilanka", "West Indies", "Bangladesh"],
    "answer": "West Indies"
  },
  {
    "number": 96,
    "question": "Chief Information Officer of India:",
    "options": ["Deepak Sandhu", "Sushama Singh", "Deepa Goyal", "Gopika Kelkhar"],
    "answer": "Sushama Singh"
  },
  {
    "number": 97,
    "question": "Postal department launches a new PIN Code: 110201 for:",
    "options": [
      "Parliament of India",
      "Prime Minister's Office",
      "Supreme Court of India",
      "Delhi High Court"
    ],
    "answer": "Parliament of India"
  },
  {
    "number": 98,
    "question": "Malala Yousafzai's autobiography \"I am Malala\" is co-written by:",
    "options": ["Christopher Joseph", "Charles Worth", "Catherine Lewins", "Christina Lamb"],
    "answer": "Christina Lamb"
  },
  {
    "number": 99,
    "question": "In protest against British Policy \"Individual Civil Disobedience\" was started under the leadership of:",
    "options": ["Thilak", "Gokhale", "Patel", "Gandhiji"],
    "answer": "Gandhiji"
  },
  {
    "number": 100,
    "question": "The architect of Human Rights Declaration:",
    "options": ["Humphry David", "John David", "John Locke", "John Peters Humphry"],
    "answer": "John Peters Humphry"
  }
]